Damn !
In the state capital today , the legislature is winding up the current session
and by this time next week all representatives will be involved
wooing constituents for next springs primary .
The weather bureau marks the current Victoria County
temperature of 98 degrees and climbing . A high of a 102 is predicted .
Looks like Woody 's farm did it again .
What happened ?
The next time we go on a trip , I 'm riding this Jeep with you guys .
Look at the size of that hole !
- Didn 't you bring a spare ? - Of course ! Woody came prepared .
Only didn 't have any air in it .
He went off to the gas station .
He 'll never find one on this old road .
Serves him right .
Poor thing ! I 'll bet his feet are aching .
Hello ?
Hey , can I get some service ?
Hello !
Anybody back here ?
Excuse me .
Ma 'am ...
Open the door .
Open the door !
Let me go !
Look , where you going we 're hot all over those springs .
You know , these tourist traps are all alike ...
They give you a big billboard , and when you get there ...
there 's nothing but a roadside shack and a bunch of cheap drinking .
Look !
It 's Woody 's tyre .
He must have gone this way , right ?
Okay .
What happened ?
I don 't know .
- What 's wrong ? - I don 't know , man .
What happened ?
I never had any trouble with this thing before .
Shit !
Let me know when you get your act together , sweetheart .
What do you think it is , Jerry ?
Well , I 'm a law student . What do I know about cars ?
- Hey you guys , come take a look at this ! - What is it ?
I don 't know ... I think it 's paradise !
And you thought this was a cheap tourist trap !
Well , I don 't know about you guys , but I 'm going swimming !
I don 't think you should .
Come on Molly . Relax for a while .
- We can 't go swimming anyway . - Why not ?
- We didn 't bring our bathing suits . - So ?
Who needs a bathing suit ?
Howdy ?
You kids enjoying yourselves ?
How about you , Missy ? You look to be having a good time .
Yes , sir .
Used to be I charge 75 cents a day to swim here .
Not no more though .
Used to be I 'd have 25 to 30 visitors a day here .
But then the government decided to build a new highway .
What is your name ?
- Molly . - Molly ?
Hey , I like that .
I do not get many visitors , no more .
It seems that most folks are using the new highway .
I guess they figured , it 's gonna get them to where they 're going fast .
Everyone is in such a damn hurry these days !
Do you know why that is , Molly ?
I don 't either .
There 's not a place like this in the whole world .
What bring you kids to this parts anyway ?
We didn 't mean to trespass ...
- Our friend got lost . - A friend ?
You see it ...
Their car broke down .
This friend of yours ... she a girl too ?
No , he 's a he . His name is Woody !
Well , I can 't help you . Ain 't see no one in these parts for weeks now .
I thought I 'd better come down and warn you .
You all best leave before it gets dark .
What happens at dark ?
Obviously a hole fills up with water moccasins .
If you feel something wiggling around you feet
it 's just the early ones comes out finding a good spot .
Hey , you guys all right ?
- Some old geezer ran us off . - He didn 't run us off .
- Well , he was weird . - Yes .
- I felt sorry for him . - Oh , yeah ?
Well how do you know he wasn 't some crazy old coop
like to chop up pretty girls by moonlight .
Yeah , they always get the pretty ones first .
Well , if that 's the case , then you girls have absolutely nothing to fear .
Very funny , Carl deGraaf .
What seems to be the trouble , young fella ?
Umm . Not sure . Can 't get it started .
- But I 'm not much of a mechanics . - Well , maybe I can help out .
Why don 't you kids hop aboard ? We 'll drop by the house for my tools .
Well , it 's just down the road , a piece in .
Well , we really appreciate that , Mr. Slausen !
My pleasure , Molly . My pleasure .
Well , come on kids ! Come on !
Welcome to Slausen Museum . Now gone out of business .
Come on in kids ! Have a look around .
I decorated it myself .
Where did you get all these junk ?
Oh it 's junk alright . I 'm just a collector at heart .
I can 't seem to bring myself to throw anything away .
See my wife passed away just after they finished the highway .
And the look of that is , these junk , my memories .
Let 's have that beer I promised you .
Here we are .
Here you are Molly .
It 's too bad you had to close this place down , Mr. Slausen .
- I 'm real sorry . - Well , thank you , thank you Molly .
But hell , that ain 't the worst thing that ever happened to me .
Hell I was kicked out of the Navy when I was 19 , kicked in the head when I was 20 ,
... and kicked into jail when I was 21 .
And that was just to warm me up for what life had in store for me .
No sir , it 's been a lot worse .
You get to be my age , you start to understand what living is all about .
This is so life like !
Yeah , my brother got pretty good at making those figures .
Your brother made these ?
And he got so good , they hired him away from me . Folks out in the city did it .
He 's out there still making dummies for one of them Wax Museums .
And watch this ...
Pretty good heh ?
Used to scare the hell out of kids and Yankee tourists .
That 's quite a killing . How did you do that ?
No , my brother did that .
He was real good with mechanical things too you know .
Gears , motors , pulleys all that sort of stuff .
He was a real talent .
Is that where you live ?
Nope .
I live right here in the museum .
- Who lives over there ? - Well ...
Nobody really .
Just Davey .
Who is Davey ?
Well , Davey Crockett , who else !
You see , he and General Custer here couldn 't get along ,
... so I had to separate them .
You girls mind guarding the place while me and Jerry fix up his Jeep .
Guard it from what ?
Oh , souvenir hunters .
Mr. Slausen !
- Can I use your phone ? - Oh sure , help yourself !
But it doesn 't work .
I got nobody to call .
Oh if you are thinking about wandering around outside ...
I wouldn 't if I were you .
- Why not ? - Well , I just wouldn 't ...
it 's not safe at night . We got trouble with coyotes .
Be back directly .
Something funny about that man .
He 's lonely .
Likes living in the past , that 's all .
Something funny about that house too .
I don 't think Mr. Slausen wants you fooling around out there .
Look , he 's hiding something . I mean , why else would he want us to stay away ?
- Who cares ? - Aren 't you curious ?
- Nope . - Well , I am .
Beside , Davey may have a phone that works .
Eileen , don 't go out there .
If I 'm not back in 10 minutes inform the posse .
Hello ?
Okay by me , I just assumed ...
Oh , my God .
Eileen ...
Woody ? Is that you ?
Woody ?
Eileen ...
Look at this !
Look at her features .
Aren 't they strange ?
Kind of looks like she could move .
What 's the matter ?
Feels like flesh .
Oh , you 're right !
Must be made out of some special rubber or something .
I don 't want to look at it anymore .
Molly , it 's only a mannequin .
- Did you hear that ? - Mm hmm .
- Did you see anything ? - No .
I scared you , didn 't I ?
You should see your face ! It 's white as a sheet .
Excuse me , Mr. Slausen .
No .
We didn 't hear your truck .
That 's because Jerry took it to town .
I walked up . Hell , we couldn 't fix that Jeep of his .
Nice boy that Jerry . Got a real head on his shoulders .
- You two are married long ? - Oh , a while .
Yeah , you be good to him , you hear .
It 's real important a wife take good care of her husband .
- You know what I 'm saying ? - Yeah .
My wife was the best thing that ever happened to me .
What a charmer she was !
She could talk the birds right down out of the trees .
And a worker too , Molly . A real good worker .
Man can 't ask much more than that , can he ?
She could make a pot of chilly , make your mouth water just thinking about them .
We were gonna make this place into a real fine resort .
She wanted to build a nice hotel ...
down by the spring .
She died so young .
It was cancer that killed her .
She died in my arms .
I 'm sorry .
It should have been me .
I 'm sorry , I ...
I get carried away sometimes .
Where is that other girl ?
Oh hmm ... she went outside .
I thought I told her not to .
Well , she ... said she just wanted to cool off .
I 'll bet she 's snooping around outside .
Davey ?
Davey , are you there ?
Davey .
Oh , my God !
What are you looking at ?
Mr. Slausen 's photo album .
This must be his brother .
You 're a regular little snoop , Molly .
It was on the coffee table .
Mr. Slausen might not be too happy if he found you checking through his pictures .
- Becky ! - What ?
Look at this !
- It 's probably his wife . So what ? - Don 't you see ?
See what ?
She looks just like that mannequin there .
You 're right . How weird !
It seems this is the mannequin of his wife .
I don 't know .
Maybe it 's just his way of remembering her .
I loved her very much .
I wanted to keep her memory alive forever .
This was the best way I know how .
That 's the whole purpose of wax museums , you know .
Keep the memory of the past alive .
And it 's easier for me this way .
- She was very beautiful . - She still is .
Where 's Eileen ?
I didn 't find her . She ...
probably went back down to the jeep .
- By herself , without telling us ? - Or where else could she be ?
- What are you doing ? - I 'm going to find her !
With a gun ?
Alright , without a gun .
Mr. Slausen !
Can we go with you ?
It 's best you ladies stay put , right here .
Stay put , my ass !
Becky !
- Don 't go . - I have to !
No you don 't . You can stay here and wait for Jerry .
I 'm going .
Alright !
I 'll come with you .
But I think we 're making a mistake .
Did you hear that ?
Mm Hmm . That is Eileen 's laugh !
I 'll bet you 10 bucks I know she 's in there .
Woody . What if you have some lucky farm boy . It has to be , Woody .
Then why don 't let those two a few minutes in his house ?
We got to climb the patios and get the hell at them .
- No , leave them alone . - They deserve this !
Come on , Becky . I 've had all the excitement I can take for one day .
I 'm going back . Let 's go .
- Chicken ! - That 's right !
- Now , let 's go . - I 'm going in .
Then you 're going in alone , because I 'm going back .
Becky !
Come on , you 've got no business going in there !
Eileen !
I 'm in here .
Woody !
I ... I know you 're in here .
I 'm in ...
Woody .
Come on !
Are we through ?
Jesus !
Come on , guys .
Look , that 's not funny .
You 're beginning to scare me .
Please .
Becky .
Eileen !
Eileen ?
Eileen , is that you ?
Eileen !
Open the door !
I brought you a visitor .
You are so pretty .
No , please ! Not again !
Why don 't you like me ?
Beck ?
Becky !
Jerry !
Are you alright ?
Who is he ?
Slausen 's crazy brother .
Where are the others ?
I don 't know .
What 's he going to do to us ?
He 's going to kill us .
I was stopping for gas along the highway .
I never even saw him coming .
He 's crazy .
We 're all going to die !
We are going to have a party !
How do I look , huh ? How do I look ?
Well , here we are .
Here we are .
Drink .
Leave her alone !
You can 't get away .
- This is for you . - No .
No ... ?
It doesn 't matter .
It 's time . The party 's over .
Oh , you 're so pretty .
It 's a shame you have to die .
No !
It 'll be quick .
But it won 't be easy .
You 'll die of fright .
Please .
It feels good , doesn 't it , huh ?
Cool and soothing .
It 's funny about plastic . As it starts to dry
it gets very hot , almost burning the skin .
You 'll panic as I seal the lips .
And now the eyes .
Oh , your face is burning now . The plastic is getting tight .
Your world is dark .
You 'll never see again .
It 's getting hard to breathe , isn 't it ?
I 'm going to seal the last hope .
You won 't be able to breathe , but you won 't suffocate .
Your heart will burst from fright before you lose consciousness .
Yes
Now ...
you are one of us ...
Isn 't she pretty ?
Stop it !
Oh , my God .
She is a pretty girl .
My brother didn 't know about her .
I kept her hidden here .
He doesn 't know much , my brother .
He 's kind of stupid !
All he cares about is that foolish museum of his .
I hate him !
One day I 'm going to get rid of him .
He should let me go to the city .
I could work for the Wax Museum .
Oh how much I hate him .
He makes me wear these stupid masks .
Do you know why ?
Because I 'm handsome .
I 'm better looking than he is .
He doesn 't like his wife to see me .
He is afraid she 'll be attracted to me .
He thinks I stay here all the time .
He doesn 't know what I really do .
I go out .
People don 't come here anymore , so I have to go out to the highway .
The gas station is perfect .
That 's where I found Tina .
She 's so pretty !
Pretty good trick , huh ?
My brother doesn 't like me to do that stuff .
He pretends he doesn 't even know about my power .
But it feels good when I use it .
I shouldn 't have to hide it !
I mean I can control it ! I can !
I shouldn 't have to hide it ! It feels good !
But it scares me .
Sometimes I really don 't know what I 'm doing .
Isn 't she pretty ?
Eileen !
Who is it ?
Molly .
Somebody 's there ! I can hear you !
Come on , you guys ! Quit fooling around with me !
Seen my friend ?
Wait , little girl .
Little girl !
See my friend !
- Molly ! - Little girl .
Molly !
Don 't go away , little girl .
See my friend !
Molly !
- Help me ! - Good Lord girl ! What happened to you ?
He 's trying to kill me !
Get us out of here ! Hurry !
What happened to you ? What 's the matter ?
This ... thing ...
- It 's out there ! - Alright , calm down now Molly .
Calm down . You 're safe with me .
What , was it an animal scared you like this ?
No . It was some kind of horrible man !
What did this thing look like ?
He was wearing ...
He was wearing some kind of mask .
Oh , dear God .
That man was my brother .
You are hiding him , aren 't you ?
You don 't understand , Molly . He never hurt anyone before .
He killed Woody !
And probably the others , for all we know .
I was only trying to protect him . Take care of him !
He is my brother !
It 's not his fault , he 's the way he is .
We have to get the police .
I 'm sorry , but we have to !
Well Molly , maybe I better find him first .
Bring him in myself .
No , no ! He 's too dangerous !
What mask was he wearing ?
Looks like a doll 's face .
He 's trying to look like me when I was a little boy .
He always wanted to be like me .
You see , I am his big brother .
He always wanted everything I ever had .
Including my face .
Look , I 'm gonna stop at the house and turn on the radio .
- He always comes to the radio . - No , no . I won 't go back there .
Now I don 't want them to shoot him down like an animal .
I just want to get him back to the house .
So I 'll know where to find him , when I get back from the police .
Alright , what I 'm going to do is turn on the radio .
You don 't even have to come in .
- I 'm coming with you ! - I 'll only be a second !
I 'm just going to set the radio in the window and turn it on .
I 'm scared ! I don 't want to be alone .
Hop out .
Now I 'm going to cork this . Now here !
If you see anybody not invited , point this at him and they 'll leave .
I don 't know how to shoot .
Honey , just point and pull the trigger . That thing will do the rest .
Mr. Slausen !
Mr. Slausen ! Are you coming ?
Mr. Slausen ! Did you hear me ?
Mr. Slausen !
Thank you God .
Okay , Mr. Slausen ! Let 's go , please !
Mr. Slausen !
Little girl .
Then you shot me
with blanks .
Bang , bang , you 're dead .
You !
Jerry !
Molly !
Jerry .
Jerry !
This is a blade or something .
Alright ...
Try slide it over here .
I got it !
It 's nice and hot .
No .
There now ... that 's better .
Go on .
Eat your soup .
- How 's that ? - Let 's eat .
That 's what I said . Let 's eat .
- It 's good ? - Yes , it 's very good .
You want some crackers ?
- I 'd like some more crackers , please . - That 's what I said .
- Yes , the crackers are very good . - Are the crackers good ?
Oh , I got to fix that .
Did you see something ?
Shhh . Be still and don 't fidget so much .
You can 't get away from me , mister .
What on earth has happened to you , child .
Now you just take it easy .
I 'll have you scrubbed it up in no time .
Alright , there you are .
I 'll just get my doctoring kit .
Mr. Slausen !
Just a minute .
Becky !
Woody ?
Woody .
Wake up , little girl .
Little girl .
Come on , girl .
Everybody 's waiting .
Come on ! Up !
There we are !
Little girl . You look tired .
I want to sleep .
Oh please .
Stop !
It 's time .
- What are going to do to me ? - Don 't talk !
This used to be my brother 's room .
He 's dead now .
I trusted him . He was a good man .
I always gave him anything he ever wanted .
What are you going to do to me ?
Do to you , Molly ? I 'm going to take care of you .
Here , here . This will warm you up some .
You 're not like the others .
There 's something special about you .
Isn 't my wife pretty ?
You remind me of her .
Yeah , yeah .
That 's why you 're so special .
There .
Please don 't .
Mr. Slausen !
Molly .
Talk to me .
Tell me you love me .
Tell me .
I love you .
I killed her .
I killed the both of them .
Her and my brother .
They were whoring behind my back .
Whoring in my own house !
Well , she and him had to die .
I got a legal right to that .
That 's what the Law says ...
A man finds his wife cheating on him .
He 's got a legal right to kill them both .
Afterwards , I missed her .
That 's when I decided to make that figure of her ,
the woman in the museum .
I kept her alive that way !
I didn 't really want to kill them .
Not really .
It was like ...
I couldn 't control myself !
Molly !
Jerry !
Jerry ?
- Jerry ! - Molly !
Come on , Molly !
Come on .
- Where are the others ? - I don 't know where they have gone .
It 's okay , it 's all over . We 're going home .
- Now , where are the others ? - Others ?
- What are you talking about ? - You know what I 'm talking about .
The other girls , Eileen and Becky .
Kill him , Jerry .
Come on Slausen , I 'm not playing games with you . Where are they ?
- I don 't wanna have to hurt you . - You don 't want to have to hurt me ?
You ?
Kill him , Jerry ! Kill him !
He can 't , Molly .
No .
This is not happening .
Oh , but it is , Molly . Look around !
They are alive !
No !
All be alive , Molly !
Join us , join us ...